Finding Aid of the UW-Milwaukee Student Union Collection, 1948-2015
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
UW-Milwaukee Student Union Collection, 1948-2015
UWM Archival Collection 124
Accession 2015-008
21.5 cubic ft. (57 boxes) 1 oversize folder 118 digital image files (57 MB) 32 digital video files (18.5 GB) plus additions of 5.2 cubic feet (6 boxes) and 455 digital files (2 GB)
University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee Libraries, Archives Department
Records of the UW-Milwaukee Student Union, including annual reports, event files, news clippings, and publications of its various departments. The collection largely consists of programming folders, flyers, and videos documenting the activities sponsored by the Union and its programming departments (Sociocultural Programming, Art Gallery, Union Cinema, Gasthaus, and Distinguished Lecture Series). Also included are handbooks, guides, and other brochures introducing the union and its services, programming brochures and reports, and issues of the Union News (1964-1978) and the Preview (1979-2009). Materials describing the activities of the Union Theatre and Union Cinema, including festivals, are particularly well represented.
The UW-Milwaukee Student Union opened in 1956 and was expanded and remodeled numerous times to accommodate a growing student population. The UW-Milwaukee Student Union is a cultural, social, and recreational center for the UWM community, housing an art gallery, bookstore, cinema, recreation center, craft centre, food service and dining areas, as well as meeting rooms and offices, including those of student organizations. The Union Policy Board is responsible for formulating and setting policy for the overall operation of the Union.
The collection contains a large amount of material relating to the administration of the Student Union, including materials related to building construction and governance, and annual reports from each of the main functional sub-departments of the Union. The bulk of the collection is comprised of materials from the programming departments, including annual programming notes, flyers and posters, correspondence with speakers, and in some cases audio or video recordings of events. Also included are press clippings relating to the Student Union gathered from a diverse selection of publications between 1948 and 2009.
The collection is arranged as eight series:
The General Files document those aspects of Union history not directly related to a particular programming unit, including files on units with no programming responsibility (such as the Bookstore). The Programming Yearbooks, which comprise core documentation for events held at the Union, contain publicity materials, event summaries, and budgets for events held by various Union departments. A large number of Annual Reports, covering the period 1981-1999, provide summaries of the year-long operations of the various Student Union departments, including summaries of events, budgets, and program evaluations and recommendations. The Union Surveys, ranging from 1988 to 2000, include raw data and prepared reports detailing the reaction of the student body to the various Union programming events. The clippings files, containing information on local media coverage of Union events, can be found in this subseries.
The Governance Files include records of committees and governing bodies responsible for setting policy for various units of the Union. The bulk of these records are from the Union Policy Board, a group comprised of students, faculty, and staff that helps set policies on issues of interest to Union users. Also included are records of smaller committees that set policy on specialized issues, such as the Arts Board and the Activities Board.
The Sociocultural Programming Files primarily consist of publicity documents, planning notes, budgets, and correspondence. The files include information on a number of regular events held by the department, including Interfest and the Multicultural Breakfast. Other files deal with speakers, panel discussions, special events, and forums held by the Sociocultural Programming Department during this time, including speakers Albin Seaborg and Toni Morrison, as well as special programs such as African Market Days and the Ebony Ball. Most of the videos in the Student Union collection were produced by Sociocultural Programming, and include recordings of lectures from figures such as Angela Davis and Wilma Mankiller, as well as more general programs such as The Midwest Affirmative Action Debate and Bags, Brooms, Bottles, and Bedcovers: HooDoo Folk Beliefs in Fine Arts.
The Distinguished Lecture Series Files includes materials related to speakers on issues of national significance, such as Cornel West, Harry Wu, Nikki Giovanni, Naomi Wolf, and Juan Williams. Materials in this series are primarily comprised of correspondence with speakers, promotional material for events, and occasionally feedback on events from participants. The series includes videos for some programs.
The Union Art Gallery Files and Gasthaus Entertainment Series Files are comprised almost exclusively of promotional material for events and exhibits. The Union Cinema Files include promotional materials of film screenings and some named film series, such as the Asian Film Festival, the Festival of Films in French, the Latin American Film Series, and the Milwaukee LGBT Film/Video Festival.
The Publications series consists of publications by Union departments. The most comprehensive of these is Preview, the monthly event calendar for the Union, which describes all scheduled programming events in the Union beginning in 1979. There are other, smaller publications that may also be of interest, including student handbooks, Craft Centre brochures, and the annual art calendar released by the UWM Bookstore.
The collection is arranged into the following series and subseries:
General Files, 1948-2011
Governance Files, 1956-1994
Sociocultural Programming Files, 1988-2012
Union Art Gallery Files, 1982-2010
Distinguished Lecture Series Files, 1982-2007
Union Cinema Files, 1978-2015
Gasthaus Entertainment Series Files, 2001-2005
Publications, 1963-2009
Files in series 1-4 and Series 8 are arranged alphabetically by folder heading. Files in series 5-7 are arranged chronologically, and thereunder alphabetically. Videos are housed separately from paper files.
Files in boxes 48-50 were segregated for reasons of size or format, but are otherwise arranged according to the series to which they belong.
The collection contains one additional accession.
Accession 2015-008: Event Files and Photographs, 1981-2015
A spreadsheet with file-level information on the electronic records is available in the Archives department. The spreadsheet contains information on original file name, file size, date and time of creation of original file, duration (where applicable) and software used to create the file. Additional technical metadata is available in the Archives; see an archivist for more information.
Administrative/Restriction Information
Electronic records must be viewed in the Archives. See an archivist for more information.
There are no access restrictions on the materials, and the collection is open to all members of the public in accordance with state law.
Most of the publications in the original collection appear to have been collected by Archives staff. Other materials were transferred to the Archives prior to 1989. Fran Ginter periodically transferred Sociocultural Programming materials to the Archives between 1991 and 1995. Union staff transferred accession 2008-019 in September 2008, accession 2010-032 in November 2010, accession 2011-006 in August 2011, accession 2011-019 in November 2011, accession 2011-025 in December 2011, accession 2011-046 in May 2012, and accession 2011-047 in June 2012. Accession 2015-008 was transferred to the Archives in September 2015.
As of December 13, 2013, all electronic files were accessible on a Intel Core 2 Duo CPU (2.33 GHz, 1.95 GB RAM) running Windows XP Professional Version 2002, with Service Pack 3. Windows Media Player was used to access the files.
The collection contains records in the following formats:
Audio/Video Interleaved Format [.avi]
JPEG File Interchange Format [.jpg]
MPEG-4 Media File [.mp4]
Contents List
- Records, 1948-2015, UWM Archival Collection 124; 21.5 cubic ft. (57 boxes) 1 oversize folder 118 digital image files (57 MB) 32 digital video files (18.5 GB)
  - 1. General Files, 1948-2011
    - 55 and Over Program
      - Activities, 1976-1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Budgets, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Bylaws, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Newsclippings, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Newsletter, 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Senior Fair, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Steering Committee, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Addition Documents, 1972-1982 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Adventure Center, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Alcohol Awareness Week, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Anniversary Parties
      - 10th Anniversary, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
      - 25th Anniversary, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
      - Union and UWM Materials, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Annual Reports
      - 1981-1990 (Box 2, Folder 4-12)
      - 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 1-19)
      - 1994-1998 (Box 4, Folder 1-22)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 5, Folder 1-8)
    - Back to School Celebration
      - 1985 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 9-15)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
    - The Bacon Brothers, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Ballet Folklorico, "Quetzalli" de Veracruz, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Bembenek, Lawrencia, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Brochures, 1961-1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 1982-1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Calendar of Events, 1960-1969 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Carter, Suzanne, Before We Die, 2001, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 53, Video 10)
    - Centennial
      - 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
      - Legal-Sized Materials, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Children's Holiday Festival, 2000-2001, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 3-5)
    - Christmas Party Photographs, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Chronology Documents, 1948-1996 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Concert Series, 1990-2000 (Box 8, Folder 7-11)
    - Conference '73 Guide, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Construction Information Reports, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Construction Photos, undated (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
    - A Conversation with Miriam Tlali, 1989, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 51, Video 6)
    - Cosmic Tales of Orishas, 2003, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 54, Video 5)
    - Craft Centre Brochures, 1974-1989 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - An Evening With...
      - Chris Eyre, 2003, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 54, Video 8)
      - Madame F, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Event Files, 1987-1988, 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - Event Flyers, 1974-2011 (Box 9, Folder 3-5)
    - Family Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Fashion Show, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Fiscal Year Overview, 1993-1996 (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
    - Fisher, Helen E., 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Glave, Thomas, 2003, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 54, Video 11)
    - Handbooks, 1958-1968 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Health Fair, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - History Documents, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Homecoming, 1982-1986 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
    - Interarts Program for Grant Writing, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - International Club, 1963-1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Irish Week, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - IRS Tax Seminar, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Kamenetz, Anya, 2007, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 57, Video 1)
    - Ladysmith Black Mambazo, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Lectures, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Series, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Leukemia Society of America, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Logo Contest, undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Lunch With Santa
      - Program, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Video, undated, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 57, Video 8)
    - Lyrical Sanctuary, undated
    - Madisalsa, 1997, Videocassette(VHS) (Box 55, Video 4)
    - Mandela, Maki, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Marketing, 2006-2008 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - McBride-Phillips Panel Discussion, 2006, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 55, Video 4)
    - McCormick, Maureen, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - McGivern, John, 2005, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 55, Video 11)
    - Meeting Facilities, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Meltdown to Midterms
      - 2001 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - 2002 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Membership Policy, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Milwaukee Initiative II, 1993-1998 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Minsky, Leonard, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Events, 2006-2008 (Box 11, Folder 5-6)
    - NACA Regional Conference Documents, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 7-8)
    - Natyarpana, 2004, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 53, Video 2)
    - New Student Orientation Production Book, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Newsclippings
      - 1948-1966 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - 1973-1982 (Box 11, Folder 11-13)
      - 1983-1990 (Box 12, Folder 1-5)
      - 1987-1995, 2003 (Box 13, Folder 1-8)
    - Operations Year-End Reports, 1981-1986 (Box 14, Folder 1-4)
    - Organization Charts, 1966-1970 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Outing Club, 2003-2008, undated (Box 14, Folder 6-10)
    - Panther Orientation, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Panther Safari, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Phase II Documents, 1971-1972 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Photography, undated (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Popcorn Forum
      - 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - 1994-1997 (Box 15, Folder 1-7)
      - Infobahn, 1994, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 52, Video 7)
    - Posters, Miscellaneous Events, 1976, undated (Oversize 1)
    - Poussaint, Alvin, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Powell, Second Keynote Address, 2006, Videocassette(VHS) (Box 56, Video 8)
    - Power Sessions, New Student Orientation/Panther Orientation, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Programming
      - 1980s Compilations
        - 1981-1984 (Box 16, Folder 1-3)
        - Oversized Materials, 1981-1984 (Box 48, Folder 5-9)
      - Yearbook
        - 1985-1991 (Box 16, Folder 4-7)
        - 1991-1995 (Box 17, Folder 1-8)
        - 1995-1999 (Box 18, Folder 1-8)
        - 1999-2003 (Box 19, Folder 1-8)
        - 2003-2004 (Box 20, Folder 1-7)
        - 2004-2009 (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
    - Programming Budget, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
    - Programming/Norris Health Center Cosponsorships, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
    - Programming/Sandburg, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Programming Staff, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Recreation Center, 2003-2008 (Box 22, Folder 1-3)
    - Recreation Handbooks, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Renovation Reports, 1984-1985, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Residents Night in the Union, 1990-1993 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Ribbon-Cutting Ceremony, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - A Rose is Still A Rose, 2002, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 53, Video 14)
    - September 11th Retrospective, 2002, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 54, Video 1)
    - Silk Road Theater, Precious Stones, undated, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 57, Video 9)
    - Sound Unbound/Rhythm Science, 2004, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 55, Video 8)
    - Speaker Videos, 2008-2010
    - Special Events, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 8-9)
    - Spence, Gerry
      - 1996 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Legal-Sized Materials, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 18)
      - Video, 1996, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 52, Video 12)
    - Stories and Songs with Santa
      - 1982, 1986-1989 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - 1994-1996 (Box 22, Folder 12-14)
      - 1997-1999 (Box 23, Folder 1-3)
      - Photographs, 1994-1998 (Box 50, Folder 3-4)
    - Study Day Picnic, 2000-2002 (Box 23, Folder 4-6)
    - Summer Orientation, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Survey
      - 1988-1995 (Box 23, Folder 8-15)
      - 1996-2003 (Box 24, Folder 1-7)
    - Swing Bands and In Black-and-White Events, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Tunnel of Oppression, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Union, undated, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 57, Video 10)
    - Union 10th Anniversary, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Union Slide Show, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Union Story Documents, 1985 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - UWM Birthday Party, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - UWM Idol
      - 2003 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Photos, 2003
    - UWM Photos, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - UWM Slides, Miscellaneous, undated (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Woolf and James Joyce Birthday Party, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - We Matter NOW!, 2002, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 54, Video 2-3)
    - Welcome Back Wednesdays
      - 1995 (Box 25, Folder 6-7)
      - 2000 (Box 25, Folder 8-9)
    - Welcome Week, 2007 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Winter Chillout
      - 1992-2000 (Box 26, Folder 2-11)
      - Photographs, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - YAWO, 2004, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 53, Video 2)
  - 2. Governance Files, 1956-1994
    - Activities Board, 1956-1971 (Box 26, Folder 12-13)
    - Art Committee, 1956-1973 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Constitution and Bylaws, 1956-1972 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Film Committee, 1963-1967 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Forum Committee, 1960-1967 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Music Committee, 1956-1971 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Social Committee, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Theatre-Literary Committee, 1965-1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Travel-Adventure Committee, 1965-1974 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Union Policy Board
      - Constitution, 1983-1985 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Documents, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 10-13)
      - Executive Committee, 1968-1987 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Minutes
        - 1963-1986 (Box 28, Folder 1-6)
        - 1987-1994 (Box 29, Folder 1-7)
  - 3. Sociocultural Programming Files, 1989-2013
    - Achieving Social Justice, 1992, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 51, Video 11)
    - Affirmative Action Debate, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - African Market Days, 1991 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - African Origins of Judaism, 1998, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 53, Video 5)
    - Afro-Cuban All Stars
      - 2001 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Photos, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Ayo, Damali, 2004, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 55, Video 10)
    - Bernstine, Daniel, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Beyond the Dream, 2007, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 57, Video 3)
    - Black Issues in Higher Education, 2007, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 57, Video 4)
    - Campus Response to Racial Harassment, undated, Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 57, Video 5-6)
    - Caribbeanfest, 2009
    - Castillo, Ana, 1999, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 53, Video 6)
    - Cyrille, Andrew
      - Concert, 1988, Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 51, Video 1-2)
      - Workshop, 1988, Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 51, Video 3-5)
    - Demerson, Bamidele, Bags, Brooms, Bottles, and Bedcovers: HooDoo Folk Beliefs in Fine Arts, 2003, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 54, Video 6)
    - Demott, Benjamin, 1998 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Diversity: Division or Unity?, 1991, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 51, Video 14)
    - Diversity Night, undated, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 53, Video 14)
    - Face to Face: An International Celebration, 2001-2002 (Box 30, Folder 6-7)
    - Faludi, Susan
      - 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Photographs, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Video, 1993, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 51, Video 13)
    - Fernandez, Wade, 2004, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 55, Video 2)
    - Forums, 1990-1998 (Box 30, Folder 9-11)
    - Heritage Day, 1996, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 52, Video 11)
    - Hicks, Joe, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Interfest
      - 1991-1996 (Box 31, Folder 2-5)
      - Gala Night Photos, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Market Days Photos, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Photos, 1993-1997 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - International Celebration, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - International Festival, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Islamic Issues in the 21st Century, Photos, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Ko-Thi, 2002, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 53, Video 11)
    - Lemelle, Anthony, Black Men: Endangered/Engendered "Species", 2003, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 54, Video 7)
    - Marable, Manning
      - 2003 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - The Struggle Continues, 1993, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 52, Video 3)
    - Mankiller, Wilma, Contemporary Tribal Issues, 1993, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 52, Video 10)
    - Menchu Tum, Rigoberta, 2005, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 55, Video 13)
    - The Midwest Affirmative Action Debate, 1997, Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 53, Video 3-4)
    - Morrison, Toni, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
    - Music of Black Milwaukee, 2005, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 55, Video 14)
    - A Night in Bronzeville, 2005, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 56, Video 3)
    - Peltier, Leonard, Panel Discussion, 1996 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Pozner, Jennifer, Heroines and Hellions, 2004, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 55, Video 3)
    - Programming
      - 1989-1991 (Box 32, Folder 4-8)
      - 1991-1993 (Box 33, Folder 1-6)
      - 1993-1996 (Box 34, Folder 1-8)
      - 1996-2005 (Box 35, Folder 1-9)
      - 2005-2008 (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
      - Co-Sponsored Programs, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - The Road to Brown, 1991, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 51, Video 7)
    - Roumain, Daniel, 2002, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 56, Video 13)
    - S.C.O.P.E., 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Seaborg, Albin, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Southeast Asian Cultural Program, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Steele, Shelby, The Content of Our Character, 1993, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 52, Video 2)
    - Tibetan Monks, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - The True Face of Islam, 1997, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 53, Video 2)
    - Unravelling the Knot of Race, 2005, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 56, Video 2)
    - Wattleton, Faye
      - 1993 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - Video, 1993, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 52, Video 1)
    - Willie, Charles, 1990, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 51, Video 7)
  - 4. Union Art Gallery Files, 1982-2010
    - Programming
      - 1982-1983 (Box 36, Folder 7-8)
      - 1984-1991 (Box 37, Folder 1-7)
      - 2003-2010 (Box 38, Folder 1-7)
    - Spring Evening Performances, 1999 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - 5. Distinguished Lecture Series Files, 1982-2007
    - 1982
      - Lundkvist, Artur (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Moody-Johnston Debate (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - O'Casey, Eileen (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Teatro Vivo de Guatemala (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - 1988
      - Cisneros, Henry (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Jemison, Mae (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - 1990
      - Bilingual Education: Help or Hindrance? (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Sontag, Susan (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - 1991
      - Gates, Henry Louis Jr.
        - Program (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - Decentering the Humanities, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 51, Video 9)
        - Video, 2007, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 57, Video 2)
      - Yevtushenko/Ragan
        - Lecture (Box 39, Folder 2-3)
        - Poetry and Politics, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 51, Video 10)
    - 1992
      - Updike, John
        - Program (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - Video, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 51, Video 11)
    - 1993
      - McPhee, John, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - 1994
      - Eban, Abba
        - Program (Box 39, Folder 6)
        - The Political Legacy of Golda Meir, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 52, Video 4)
      - Giovanni, Nikki (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Kozol, Jonathan
        - Program (Box 39, Folder 8)
        - Photographs (Box 49, Folder 15)
        - Video, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 52, Video 5)
      - Nader, Ralph, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Tan, Amy, 1994, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 52, Video 6)
    - 1995
      - Anzaldua, Gloria
        - Program (Box 39, Folder 10)
        - Video, Videocassette (VHS) (Box 52, Video 8)
      - West, Cornel